William Asadorian Collection TAM.461
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
William Asadorian Collection
1720-2011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Asadorian, William
TAM.461
21.5 Linear Feet in 36 boxes
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials donated by William Ronald Asadorian in 2008, 2009, 2010, 2011, 2016, and 2008; additional materials were found in the repository inn 2009, 2011, 2017, and 2019. The accession numbers related to this collection are 2008.052, 2009.017, 2009.018, 2009.022, 2009.028, 2009.029, 2009.034, 2009.042, 2009.045, 2009.098, 2009.099, 2010.055, 2010.084, 2011.051, 2011.116, 2011.125, 2011.130, 2011.141, 2016.059, 2017.065, 2018.010, 2019.043, and 2019.044.
United States -- History -- 1783-1865.; United States -- History -- 1865-1921.; Commerce -- History -- 19th century.; Caribbean Area -- Commerce -- United States.; Receipts (financial records).; Surveys (documents).; Diaries; Asadorian, William
- Unidentified Letter, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Unidentified Letter, 1897 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1887-1943 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Unidentified Letter, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Unidentified Letter, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Correspondence of John A. Conley, Captain in the 110th Infantry Medical Detachment, April 1944-January 1945 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1900-1926 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Legal Document of Inquisition into NYC Tavern Keeper, 1759 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Correspondence of Lee Ingham, "Marvelous Hand Leaper and Equilibrist", 1895-1903 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Letter of Credit, 1777 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Supply Order, 1781 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Unidentified Letter, 1781 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Order from the Governor of Connecticut, 1775 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Letter of Credit, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Unidentified Letter, 1777 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Connecticut Council of Safety, 1780 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Loan Letter, 1777 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Court Order, 1780 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Letter of Payment, 1779 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Letter of Payment, 1782 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Connecticut State Treasury Note, 1782 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Letter of Payment for Revolutionary War Service, 1783 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Letter of Payment, 1781 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Supply Order, 1777 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Letter of Payment, 1781 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Letter of Payment, 1778 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Receipt for Salt, 1781 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Program Book for the Musical Fantasie Benefit for St. Christopher's, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Letters from George W. Doane to Mrs. Mary Warren, 1827-1835 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- England Receives Florida in 1763 Settlement, 1765 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Letter of Payment, 1779 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Photographs of New York City (29 items), 1902, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Letters and Assorted Documents, Including: Letters from Richard Morris and Oliver Ellsworth, items about the Revolutionary War, War of 1812, Connecticut, the Whig Party, and Henry Clay (54 items), Various and undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Diary of Noram Freed of Brooklyn, NY, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Legal Agreements between NY Elevated Rail Road Company and William L. Scott, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Scrapbook of Miss Florence Hacker, Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1835-1905 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Correspondence between Mr. Van Volkenburgh to Eliza A. Thorne, 1890-1895 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Dance Invitations, 1918-1945 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1893-1910 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Unidentified Letter, 1849 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Photographs: Probably of Employees of the Anaconda Copper Mining Company in Montana, Undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Unidentified Correspondence and Receipts, Various and Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Unidentified Correspondence and Receipts, Various and Undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Unidentified Correspondence and Receipts, Various and Undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Pine Plains Register (Pine Plains, NY Newspaper), 1886 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Unidentified Correspondence and Receipts, Various and Undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Unidentified Correspondence and Receipts, Various and Undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Unidentified Correspondence and Receipts, Various and Undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Unidentified Correspondence and Receipts, Various and Undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Correspondence of the Law Firm of Slade & Slade (NYC), 1912-1917 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Ephemera, Various and Undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Various Newspapers, 1865-1923 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- A Girl in Every Port Poster from Empire Theatre, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Loew's Strand Poster for A Day at the Races and The Critical Age, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Various Newspapers, Late 19th Century (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Mary McLennan: Correspondence and Documents (Includes Photos), Various and Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Mary McLennan: Correspondence and Documents (Includes Photos) (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Unidentified Correspondence and Documents, Various and Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Jewelers' League, Late 19th Century (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Unidentified Letter, 1853 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1889-1901 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Letter from George Ripley, 1878 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- United Nations, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Unidentified Correspondence, Various and Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Correspondence from Participants in the First World War, 1916-1919 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Correspondence from Carl to Mary Sigwart, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Ephemera, Various and Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
- First and Second World War Buttons and Small Book about George Washington, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Telegram Relating to Attempted Assasination of President Theodore Roosevelt, 1902 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Photographic Portraits, 1865, Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Binder of Second World War Letters, Divided by Service, 1942-1945, Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Textile of the General Israel Orphans' Home for Girls (NYC), Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
- "U.S. Treasury News Bulletin", Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Correspondence about the Battle of Little Big Horn, 1876-1890 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Correspondence from John B. Reid, 1918-1919 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Anniversary Issue of The Prospect (Publication of the Second Presbyterian Church in NYC), 1931 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Unidentified Correspondence (includes photos), 1945, Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Unidentified Document with Chinese Characters and Drawing, Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Photograph of Company B, 8th Regiment (Peekskill, NY), 1893 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Sheet Music for "My Belgian Rose", Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Unidentified Correspondence, Various and Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Binder of Unidentified Correspondence and Receipts, Various and Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Binder of Unidentified Correspondence and Documents, Various and Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Advertisment for Ellenbogen & Levy, Marshal's Bureau and Auctioneers (NYC), Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Advertisment for Waterman's Fountain Pen, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Advertisment for Performance of Duprez & Benedict Minstrels and Brass Band (Framed), Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Bound Scrapbook Honoring the Red Cross, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Scrapbook Honoring the Red Cross, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Bound Scrapbook Honoring the Red Cross, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1943-1945, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Unidentified Correspondence (Postcards), 1886-1892 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1843-1857 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Advertisments for Titus Crockery and Becker's Teas (NYC), Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Excerpt from Morning Press (Kodiak, AK), 1943 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Unidentified Correspondence and Documents, 19th Century (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Unidentified Letter, 1817 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Photograph of Men in Uniform (Probably Veterans), Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Unidentified Document, c.17th or 18th Century (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Correspondence and Documents Relating to Army Officer Peter Gansevoort, 1792-1809 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Connecticut State Resolution on Confiscating Tory Property, 1785 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Valley Stream Carnival News (Valley Stream, NY), 1911 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Court Document (NY), 1769 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Connecticut Pay Order, 1777 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Indenture Agreement (NY), 1795 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Letter from Henry Cuyler to Lou Henry Cuyler, 1733 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- John Chain Inventory and Petition to Whitehead Hicks, NYC, 1767 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Bond Agreement between NYC and James Blanchard, 1787 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Sheet Music for Song "Gypsy Trail", Undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Unidentified Correspondence, Newspapers, and Documents, Various and Undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Unidentified Correspondence and Letters of Payment, 1834-1910 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Correspondence Relating to Working Conditions at the Singer Sewing Machine Company, 1863-1911 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Trade Cards and Postcards, Mostly Depicting African-Americans, Undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1815-1859 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Stock Certificates for the NY Central Railroad Company, also Letterhead for Talmud Torah Mishkan Israel (Jamaica, NY), 1931-1957, Undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Court Documents from Vermont, 1796-1819 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- William Asadorian's M.A. Thesis "History of Tobacco," also Includes Research Notes, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Expense Report for Newgate State Prison, 1797 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Unidentified Correspondence and Documents, Various and Undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Photographs of the Equitable Life Insurance Building Fire, c. 1915 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Document Signed by Alexander Hamilton (photocopy, original placed in vault), 1792 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Unidentified Correspondence and Documents, 1824-1840 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Unidentified Correspondence and Documents, 1792-1947 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1829-1860 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Correspondence from Alan F. Johnson at the U.S. Navy Yard, Pearl Harbor to his wife Luella, 1942-1943 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Correspondence Relating to Pennsylvania in the 1880s (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1838-1853 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1836-1896 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Excerpt from the Procedings of the U.S. Senate and Pay Order, 1849-1852 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- The Investigator (Newton, NY Newspaper), 1822 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Illustrations of U.S. Cities, Undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1893-1894 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Seven Issues of The Signal (Trenton, NJ), 1899-1900 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Book titled Ada Rehan: A Study, by William Winter, 1891 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Bound copies of The American Agriculturist, Volume 16, 1857 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Bound copies of The American Agriculturist, Volume 17, 1858 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Bound copies of The American Agriculturist, Volume 18, 1859 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Scottish Journal of Intelligence and Literature (NY, 1841), Shamrock or Hiberian Chronicle (NY, 1811), and Auctioneer's Notice, 1811-1891 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Photograph of May Day Ceremony in NYC, 1925 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Sheet Music, Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Labor (Washington D.C. Newspaper), 1944-1950 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- V-E Day Issue of The Daily Record (Boston Newspaper), 1945 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Sheet Music, Various and Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Sheet Music, Various and Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Sheet Music, Various and Undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Sheet Music, Various and Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Sheet Music, Various and Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Sheet Music, Various and Undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Sheet Music, Various and Undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Sheet Music, Various and Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Metal Star of David from the Sea Gate Sisterhood Synagogue (Coney Island) (Box 8, Oversize 1)
- Photograph and Note Relating to Metal Star of David (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Facsimile of Revolutionary War Map of Bowery Farm (NYC), Undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Posters Advertising Property Auctions in NYC (8 items), 1866-1868 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Contract between Master and Seamen of the Schooner Elizabeth, 1772 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Engraving from Barnard's History of England, Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Essex Gazette (Salem), 1773 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- New York Journal or the General Advertiser, 1769 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Receipts, 1875 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1884-1940 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, Photographs, and Stamps Relating to the Red Cross, 1939-1962 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Red Cross Pamphlets, 1965, Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Unidentified Diary, 1903 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Landon/Knox Presidential Campaign: "Fact-Cards for use of Pennsylvania Republican Speakers", 1936 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Speeches of Senator F. T. Frelinghuysen (NJ) on Southern Claims, New Jersey's Railroad Policy, the Fifteenth Amendment, &c. (Pamphlet), 1869 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Correspondence from Soldiers and Sailors in the Second World War, 1942-1946 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Letter to Harriet Lockhart Regarding Tooth Extraction, 1840 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Tobacco Cards of the Series "Theatres Old and New", Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Second World War Propaganda Envelopes, 1943-1945 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Pamphlets, Early 19th Century (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Correspondence from Soldiers Serving in the American Expeditionary Force (AEF), 1918 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Pamphlets, 19th Century (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Correspondence from John A. Oliver Jr., Stationed on Guam (includes photographs), 1946, Undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1819-1850, Undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Letter from Union Soldier in U.S. Civil War, c. 1862 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Unidentified Letter, 1832 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Business Card, Undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Receipts for Expenses of Charles Blum, 1887-1895 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1918-1943 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Letter from C. Powell to Mrs. Geo. E. Powell, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Unidentified Letter, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Letter to Mrs. Kent, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Unidentified Letter, 1840 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Letter to Far Rockaway (NYC), Undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Letter to Mrs. Kent, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Letter from AEF Soldier, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Correspondence from AEF Soldier, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Correspondence from AEF Soldier, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Letter from AEF Soldier, 1917 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Correspondence from AEF Soldiers, 1918-1919 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1819-1853 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1837-1860 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Unidentified Correspondence and Receipts, 1837-1850, Undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1816-1845 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1840, Undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Poetry, c. Early 19th Century (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Unidentified Letter, 1837 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Unidentified Letter, 1811 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Tickets and Notices of Balls, 1909, 1919, Undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Photographs of the Family and Lumberyard of James F. Welch, c. Late 19th Century (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Photographic Portraits, Undated (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Photographs of the Columbus Celebration in NYC, 1892-1893 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Photographs of NYC, 1923-1924 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- New York World's Fair: Map Pamphlet, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Stock Certificates, 1899, Undated (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Photograph of 6th Avenue between 32nd and 33rd Streets (NYC), 1878 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Photographs from NYC, Undated (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Letter Relating to 1860 Presidential Campaign (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1877-1886 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Correspondence to Representative Joseph Leonard Tililinghast (RI), 1826-1840 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1845-1850, Undated (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Penny Magazine, Volume 1, 1832 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Penny Magazine, Volume 3, 1834 (Box 10, Folder 56)
- Correspondence and Diaries of the Robertson Family of New Iberia, LA, Late 19th Century (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Pamphlets and Receipts, 1835-1853 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- The Republican (NY), 1926 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Pamphlets, Receipts, and Correspondence, Various and Undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Correspondence from Soldiers and Sailors, 1942-1949 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Correspondence from Naval Personnel, Mostly Stationed in Japan, 1945-1963 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Unidentified Correspondence, Early 20th Century (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Hundreds of Love Letters to Hannah U. Harding at the Brockport Normal School (CT), from NY, c. 1906-1909 (Box 12)
- Hundreds of Love Letters to Hannah U. Harding at the Brockport Normal School (CT), from NY, c. 1906-1909 (Box 13)
- Photographs of NYC Taken by the Department of Public Services/Public Service Commission (68 items), 1902-1916 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Land Deeds, 1814-1842 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1819-1850 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1799-1861 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1839-1859, Undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Letter to J.S. Bache, Secretary of the Fortnightly, 1887 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1821-1858, Undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Unidentified Correspondence, 1782-1860 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Unidentified Letter, Undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Unidentified Letter, 1843 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Letter from Calvin S. Brice, 1889 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Flyers from the Roosevelt-Garner Campaign, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Photographs of Unidentified Musicians, c. 1940 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Various Photographs, Early 20th century (Box 15)
- Poster from Chatham Theatre, 1843 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Illustrated News (NY Newspaper), 1853-1893 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Correspondence: New Orleans to New York City, 1854 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Correspondence: Mobile, Alabama to New York City, 1842 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Correspondence: Philadelphia to London, 1793 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1848 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Ephemera, 1720 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Correspondence: From New Hampshire to Colonel Daniel Brodhead in Boston, regarding politics and presidency of Andrew Jackson, 1831 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Ephemera: Maryland, 1721 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1849 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1842 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1851 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1848 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1846 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1849 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1839 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1835 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Correspondence, 1850 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1847 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Correspondence, 1851 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1849 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Correspondence, 1842 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Correspondence, 1850 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, 1845 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Correspondence, 1849 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Correspondence, 19th century (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Correspondence, 1847 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Correspondence, 1850 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Correspondence, 1849 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Correspondence, 1850 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Correspondence, 1849 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Correspondence, 1898 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Correspondence, 1841 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Correspondence, 1850s (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Correspondence, 1845 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Correspondence, 1860 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Correspondence, 19th century (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Correspondence, 1855 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- Correspondence, 1828 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- Correspondence, 1831 (Box 17, Folder 38)
- Correspondence, 1829 (Box 17, Folder 39)
- Correspondence, 1835 (Box 17, Folder 40)
- Correspondence, 1859 (Box 17, Folder 41)
- Correspondence, 1853 (Box 17, Folder 42)
- Correspondence, 1852 (Box 17, Folder 43)
- Correspondence, 1856 (Box 17, Folder 44)
- Correspondence, 1853 (Box 17, Folder 45)
- Correspondence, 1849 (Box 17, Folder 46)
- Correspondence, 1852 (Box 17, Folder 47)
- Correspondence, 1848 (Box 17, Folder 48)
- Correspondence, 1847 (Box 17, Folder 49)
- Correspondence, 1850 (Box 17, Folder 50)
- Correspondence, 1847 (Box 17, Folder 51)
- Correspondence, 1850 (Box 17, Folder 52)
- Correspondence, 19th century (Box 17, Folder 53)
- Correspondence, 1849 (Box 17, Folder 54)
- Correspondence, 1832 (Box 17, Folder 55)
- Correspondence, 1834 (Box 17, Folder 56)
- Correspondence, 1833 (Box 17, Folder 57)
- Correspondence, 1842 (Box 17, Folder 58)
- Correspondence, 1849 (Box 17, Folder 59)
- Correspondence, 1847 (Box 17, Folder 60)
- Request for Payment, 1842 (Box 17, Folder 61)
- Correspondence, 1848 (Box 17, Folder 62)
- Correspondence, 1850s (Box 17, Folder 63)
- Correspondence, 1850 (Box 17, Folder 64)
- Correspondence, 1839 (Box 17, Folder 65)
- Correspondence, 1848 (Box 17, Folder 66)
- Correspondence, 1840s (Box 17, Folder 67)
- Correspondence, 19th century (Box 17, Folder 68)
- Correspondence, 19th century (Box 17, Folder 69)
- Correspondence, 1848 (Box 17, Folder 70)
- Correspondence, 1850 (Box 17, Folder 71)
- Correspondence, 1840s (Box 17, Folder 72)
- Correspondence, 1816 (Box 17, Folder 73)
- Correspondence, 1839 (Box 17, Folder 74)
- Supply Order, 1896 (Box 17, Folder 75)
- Correspondence, early 20th century (Box 17, Folder 76)
- Correspondence, 1849 (Box 17, Folder 77)
- Correspondence, 1847 (Box 17, Folder 78)
- Correspondence, 1844 (Box 17, Folder 79)
- Correspondence, 1848 (Box 17, Folder 80)
- Correspondence, 1840 (Box 17, Folder 81)
- Correspondence, 1845 (Box 17, Folder 82)
- Correspondence, 1833 (Box 17, Folder 83)
- Correspondence, 1845 (Box 17, Folder 84)
- Correspondence, undated (Box 17, Folder 85)
- Correspondence, 1836 (Box 17, Folder 86)
- Correspondence, undated (Box 17, Folder 87)
- Correspondence, 1834 (Box 17, Folder 88)
- Correspondence, 1842 (Box 17, Folder 89)
- Correspondence, 19th century (Box 17, Folder 90)
- Correspondence, 1848 (Box 17, Folder 91)
- Receipt, 1819 (Box 17, Folder 92)
- Correspondence, 1814 (Box 17, Folder 93)
- Correspondence, 19th century (Box 17, Folder 94)
- Correspondence, 1849 (Box 17, Folder 95)
- Correspondence, 1850 (Box 17, Folder 96)
- Request for Payment, 1840s (Box 17, Folder 97)
- Correspondence, 1847 (Box 17, Folder 98)
- Correspondence, 1819 (Box 17, Folder 99)
- Correspondence, undated (Box 17, Folder 100)
- Correspondence, 1829 (Box 17, Folder 101)
- Contract, 1821 (Box 17, Folder 102)
- Correspondence, 1858 (Box 17, Folder 103)
- Correspondence, 1848 (Box 17, Folder 104)
- Correspondence, 1846 (Box 17, Folder 105)
- Correspondence, 1832 (Box 17, Folder 106)
- Correspondence, 1865 (Box 17, Folder 107)
- Correspondence: New York, 1848 (Box 17, Folder 108)
- Pamphlet by Rev. Starks (New York), 1868 (Box 17, Folder 109)
- Ephemera, undated (Box 17, Folder 110)
- Harlem Church Directory, 1879 (Box 17, Folder 111)
- Pamphlet of Daniel Webster Speech, 1842 (Box 17, Folder 112)
- Ephemera, undated (Box 17, Folder 113)
- Ephemera, 1755 (Box 17, Folder 114)
- Receipt, undated (Box 17, Folder 115)
- Correspondence, 1829 (Box 17, Folder 116)
- Correspondence, 1840s (Box 17, Folder 117)
- Ephemera, 1758 (Box 17, Folder 118)
- Correspondence, 1829 (Box 17, Folder 119)
- Correspondence: New York, 1827 (Box 17, Folder 120)
- Correspondence, 19th century (Box 17, Folder 121)
- Correspondence: Havana to Buffalo, New York, 1848 (Box 17, Folder 122)
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 17, Folder 123)
- Ephemera: Roberts Circus - New Jersey Tour, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 124)
- Ephemera: John R. Van Arnam's Radio Funmakers (Syracuse, New York), 1930s (Box 17, Folder 125)
- Ephemera: Krakaur Poultry Company (New York City), 1937 (Box 17, Folder 126)